<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>TechCrunch</title>
	<atom:link href="https://techcrunch.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://techcrunch.com/</link>
	<description>Startup and Technology News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.8.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</url>
	<title>TechCrunch</title>
	<link>https://techcrunch.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ford and Renault team up on cheaper EVs in a &#8216;fight for our lives&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/ford-and-renault-team-up-on-cheaper-evs-in-a-fight-for-our-lives/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kirsten Korosec]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Transportation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[auto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EVs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ford]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Renault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[transportation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074185</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The automakers will work together to bring two Ford-branded EVs to European dealerships in 2028. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Photos launches new video editing tools</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/google-photos-launches-new-video-editing-tools/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lauren Forristal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google Photos]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google Photos' new update helps make editing video reels in the app quicker, such as new templates that already add music and text to clips. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NASA and USPS stop using Canoo EVs despite CEO&#8217;s pledged support</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/nasa-and-usps-stop-using-canoo-evs-despite-ceos-pledged-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sean O'Kane]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Transportation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canoo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electric vehicles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EVs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exclusive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NASA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USPS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Canoo's CEO bought the bankrupt startup's assets in April and told the court his "principal motivation" was supporting these programs.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI, Anthropic and Block join new Linux Foundation effort to standardize the AI agent era</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/openai-anthropic-and-block-join-new-linux-foundation-effort-to-standardize-the-ai-agent-era/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rebecca Bellan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI agents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linux foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mcp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[open-source]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenAI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anthropic, Block, and OpenAI  are backing the Linux Foundation’s new Agentic AI Foundation, donating MCP, Goose, and AGENTS.md to standardize AI agents, boost interoperability, and curb proprietary fragmentation.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fairphone refreshes its good-looking, repairable headphones</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/fairphone-refreshes-its-good-looking-repairable-headphones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ivan Mehta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gadgets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fairphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[headphones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[repairable]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074047</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fairphone updates its repair over-the-ear headphones with new drivers.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Facebook redesign focuses on friends, photos, Marketplace and more</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/facebook-redesign-focuses-on-friends-photos-marketplace-and-more/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Perez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[TC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gen z]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073950</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Meta's Facebook redesign elevates Marketplace, refreshes profiles, and aims to win back Gen Z users.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon adds delivery tracking, last-minute adds, gift ideas to Alexa+</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/amazon-adds-delivery-tracking-last-minute-adds-gift-ideas-to-alexa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Perez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alexa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alexa+]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[echo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shopping]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amazon upgrades Alexa+ with new shopping tools, turning Echo screens into hubs for orders, deals, and gift buying.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google&#8217;s first AI glasses expected next year</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/googles-first-ai-glasses-expected-next-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amanda Silberling]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMART Glasses]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google is working on various types of AI-powered glasses — one model is designed for screen-free assistance, using built-in speakers, microphones, and cameras to allow the user to communicate with Gemini and take photos. The other model has an in-lens display — which is only visible to the person wearing the glasses — that can show turn-by-turn directions or closed captioning.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU launches antitrust probe into Google&#8217;s AI search tools</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/eu-launches-antitrust-probe-into-googles-ai-search-tools/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ram Iyer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Government & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[antitrust ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google ai mode]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google ai overviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074143</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The European Commission is investigating Google over its AI summaries.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft to invest $17.5B in India by 2029 as AI race accelerates</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/microsoft-to-invest-17-5b-in-india-by-2029-as-ai-race-accelerates/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jagmeet Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enterprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Government & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satya Nadella]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074088</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The latest is Microsoft's largest investment in Asia.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VSCO lays off 24 staff as its consumer business suffers</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/vsco-lays-off-24-staff-as-its-consumer-business-suffers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ivan Mehta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layoffs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VSCO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In an internal memo seen by TechCrunch, VSCO's CEO Eric Wittman said the company's consumer business had declined more than expected, and some of its new growth initiatives didn't yield the expected results.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India proposes charging OpenAI, Google for training AI on copyrighted content</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/india-proposes-charging-openai-google-for-training-ai-on-copyrighted-content/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jagmeet Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Government & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai copyright]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perplexity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[India has given OpenAI, Google, and other AI firms 30 days to respond to its proposed royalty system for training on copyrighted content.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthropic and Accenture sign multi-year AI strategic partnership</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/anthropic-and-accenture-sign-multi-year-ai-strategic-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rebecca Szkutak]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enterprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accenture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[In Brief]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The two companies are launching the Accenture Anthropic Business Group to bring Anthropic's AI to Accenture's employees. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pebble&#8217;s founder introduces a $75 AI smart ring for recording brief notes with a press of a button</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/pebbles-founder-introduces-a-75-ai-smart-ring-for-recording-brief-notes-with-a-press-of-a-button/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Perez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gadgets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai ring]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[index 01]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pebble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smart ring]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073797</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Named for the finger where the ring is meant to be worn, the new $75 Index 01 ring is not meant to be a competitor to the always-on, always-listening AI devices, like the AI pendant Friend, but instead offers a way to record quick notes and reminders with a press of a button on the ring's side.

AI only comes into play via the open source, speech-to-text, and AI models that run locally on your smartphone, via the open source Pebble mobile app. That is, if the Ring's button is not being pressed, it's not recording. (And this is a press-and-hold gesture, too, which means you can't start the ring's recording and then let go to surreptitiously record a conversation.)

You can wear the stainless steel ring while in the shower, washing hands, doing dishes, or in the rain, but you would have to take it off for other water-related activities, like swimming. At launch, it's water-resistant to 1 meter.

The ring is also not a fitness tracker or sleep monitor. It doesn't record details about your heart rate or health. And it's not there to be your AI friend. 

"I'm not trying to build some AI assistant thing," Migicovsky told TechCrunch in an interview. "I build things that solve one main problem, and they solve it really well," he explains. "I think of [the ring] as external memory for my brain...that's what this is. It's always with you." 

Plus, the ring has been designed to be highly reliable and privacy-preserving, he says, as all your thoughts are stored on your phone, not in the cloud. There is no subscription. 

Migicovsky has been wearing the ring for three months now and says he cannot imagine going back to a world where he doesn't always have a memory device with him.

"The problem is that, during the day, I get ideas or I remember something, and if I don't write it down that second, I forget it," he says. The ring solves this problem, he adds, without becoming another device you need to charge. 

"The battery lasts for years," Migicovsky claims. 

Technically, the ring is said to support roughly 12 to 14 hours of recording. On average, the founder says he uses it 10-20 times per day to record 3-6 second thoughts. At that rate, he'll get about two years of usage. When the ring's battery dies, you can ship it back to the company for recycling. 

When using Index, you can record up to five minutes of audio, which can be saved to the ring and synced to your phone later. This makes sense for recording briefer, personal thoughts and notes, even when you don't have your phone handy, but it wouldn't work for recording a longer chat, like a presentation, meeting, or in-person interview of some kind.

The ring also supports 99+ languages and has a bit of on-device memory, in case you're not in Bluetooth range of your device, where the recording is ultimately saved and transcribed. (The raw audio is retained, too, in case the speech-to-text is garbled due to loud background noise). 

If you own a Pebble smartwatch or one from another brand, your recorded thought can even appear on the watch's screen so you can verify it's correct. 

The ring works with Pebble's mobile app, which offers notes and reminders, but can optionally integrate with your phone's calendaring system, too, or other apps, like Notion. And the ring's software is open source, which makes it hackable by the community, the founder points out. 

Because of its open nature, the ring's button is already programmable. In addition to the press-and-hold gesture, you can program the ring to do other things with a single or double press, like play or pause your music or control the shutter on your phone's camera. You could use it to send a message through the universal chat app Beeper, which Migicovsky also created, or you could add your own voice actions via MCP. 

A new approach to hardware 

Migicovsky acknowledges that hardware can be difficult to get right -- as the previous exit of Pebble to Fitbit showed. (Fitbit, too, was later acquired by Google in 2021). 

"I didn't earn any money during Pebble -- we exited, but it was not a great exit," Migicovsky admits.  

This year, however, he decided to reboot the Pebble project after Google open sourced the PebbleOS, which opened up the door to new hardware. 

With his new company, Core Devices, Migicovsky plans to do things differently. 

Still, the founder doesn't regret his previous choices, he clarifies.

"I wouldn't have gone back and changed anything. I loved what we built. I loved what we did. I love the company that we built, but it's not the only way to build a company," he told TechCrunch. " And, speaking as an ex-YC partner, there are -- there's a time and a place for building a venture-backed startup. Some companies are phenomenal when they raise money and build a big team, and I tried that...I think what I'm doing now is trying an alternative path, which is [to] start from profitability," he says.

The new company is a small team of five, self-funded, and focused on sustainability.

So far, Core Devices has shipped the Pebble 2 Duo smartwatch with a black-and-white display. Its first run sold out, and the company is now preparing to ship the upgraded version, the Pebble Time 2. The newer device, which has seen 25,000 pre-orders, is a stainless steel watch with a larger, color e-ink screen.   

As for the Index 01, the ring's pre-order offer ends in March 2026. After that, the price increases to $99. It currently comes in silver, polished gold, and matte black and works with iOS and Android devices. Customers can select from eight ring sizes and three colors.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spotify launches music videos in the US and Canada for Premium subscribers</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/spotify-launches-music-videos-in-the-u-s-and-canada-for-premium-subscribers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Perez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spotify]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[streaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The videos, which are provided by music labels under new agreements, will be available only to paying subscribers on Spotify's Premium plan and can be streamed on its iOS, Android, desktop, and TV apps. Spotify will let you switch between music videos and audio at any time. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mistral AI surfs vibe-coding tailwinds with new coding models</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/mistral-ai-surfs-vibe-coding-tailwinds-with-new-coding-models/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anna Heim]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai models]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mistral AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vibe coding]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074070</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[French AI startup Mistral today launched Devstral 2, a new generation of its AI model designed for coding, as the company seeks to catch up to bigger AI labs like Anthropic and other coding-focused LLMs.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empromptu raises $2M pre-seed to help enterprises build AI apps</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/09/empromptu-raises-2m-pre-seed-to-help-enterprises-build-ai-apps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dominic-Madori Davis]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enterprise]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3074061</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Empromptu claims all a user has to do is tell the platform's AI chatbot what they want — like a new HTML or JavaScript app — and the AI will go ahead and build it. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTC upholds ban on stalkerware founder Scott Zuckerman</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/ftc-upholds-ban-on-stalkerware-founder-scott-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lorenzo Franceschi-Bicchierai]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[privacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spyware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[surveillance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybersecurity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stalkerware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SpyFone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SpyTrac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073988</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Zuckerman, who used to run the stalkerware apps SpyFone and SpyTrac, claimed the ban is hurting his unrelated business. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoftBank and Nvidia reportedly in talks to fund Skild AI at $14B, nearly tripling its value</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/softbank-and-nvidia-reportedly-in-talks-to-fund-skildai-at-14b-nearly-tripling-its-value/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marina Temkin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[In Brief]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[skild ai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073981</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Skild AI is developing a hardware-agnostic foundation model for robots that can be customized for various uses.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investor letter reveals skyrocketing growth of Waymo&#8217;s robotaxi rides</title>
		<link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/12/08/investor-letter-reveals-skyrocketing-growth-of-waymos-robotaxi-rides/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kirsten Korosec]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Transportation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[autonomous vehicles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[In Brief]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robotaxi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Waymo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/?p=3073936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Six months ago, Waymo disclosed it was providing 250,000 robotaxi rides. But it's grown significantly since, a leaked letter says.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
